MAYUR BAYAS

DESKTOP SUPPORT ENGINEER L1 AND L2

I (+91) 8390163524 **PHONE**

EMAIL I baismayuresh@gmail.co

LOCATION | Pune, INDIA

EXPERIENCE I 5 Years 6 Months

Key Skills

- SLA
- VPN Server
- Active Directory Support
- LAN Troubleshooting
- Desktop Administration
- Desktop Support
- Computer Hardware
- Desktop Engineering
- Mobile Hardware Engineer
- Hardware
- Software
- Network Troubleshooting
- Hardware Support
- Hardware Installation
- IT

Certification

- TYBA
- Advance Hardware **Networking**

Profile Summary

As a Desktop Support Engineer L2, I am an expert in troubleshooting and resolving technical issues related to computer hardware, software, and networking. I possess extensive knowledge of operating systems such as Windows as well as experience with Active Directory, DNS, DHCP, and TCP/IP. I am skilled in installing, configuring and maintaining PCs, printers, scanners, and other peripherals. Additionally, I have a solid understanding of security measures and protocols and can ensure the protection of valuable data and information. My ability to communicate effectively, both verbally and in writing, allows for easy documentation of technical resolutions and interactions with endusers.

Work Experience

Desktop Support Engineer L1 and L2

3i-Infotech.pvt Ltd 04/2022 - 05/2024

desktop support Engineer L2, network admin L1,SAP configuration

Desktop Support Engineer

Gtechnosoft Pvt Ltd 05/2021 - 04/2022

desktop support Engineer, IT support four year experience in installation configuration software ticketing tool

Field Technician Engineer

- Hindhi
- Marathi
- English

TVS Electronics (Dell service centre) 04/2018 - 08/2020

desktop support Engineer L2

Field Technician Engineer L2

Aadvika Invoitec.pvt ltd (Dell service center)

09/2020 - 05/2021

Education

Bachelor of Arts - economic 2019 Open Univarcity

B.A - Fine Arts
2016
OPEN UNIVERSITY PUNE